William Rebain

Charlotte, NC Cell: 803-658-8601

28277 Email: willrebain@gmail.com

VISION

My imagination will always be an incredible driving force in my life; the influence in everything I do. With over five years' experience in developing engaging and innovative designs for clients in a broad range of industries, I strive to demonstrate success working in collaborative environments, providing leadership, and during projects which I keep creative sovereignty, to conceptualize and execute purposeful design to help clients achieve business development and business growth goals.

PERSONAL VALUES CORE COMPETENCIES

Deliver WOW Through Ideas Embrace & Drive Change Print/New Media Design
Be Passionate—Determined Be Resourceful—Open-minded Frontend Web Developer

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Walmart 2016 - 2017

Department Manager 2016

I began working as an associate in the Deli/Bakery for my local Walmart. In short time, I strived to make the management team. I saw opportunities and possibilities that were not being seized. I accomplished my goal of providing a communication between our entry-level associates and the management team; providing common ground and understanding from staff members of all levels.

Developed organization system that translates from associate point-of-view to management.

PostNET 2015 - 2016

Graphic Designer 2016

PostNet, a pack and ship store in its truest form, was a job that I found during the holiday season. A great place to work, but it is not an occupation in my field. PostNET is less print shop and aimed, alternatively, toward excellent packing service and routine printing needs.

Found market opportunity with Every Door Direct Mail campaign

Salsarita's Fresh Cantina 2014 - 2015

Catering Coordinator 2015

Beginning at the start of the line, I quickly set myself apart in my direction and attitude. I moved to the Catering department where I showed the courtesy due and the professionalism required to be Catering Coordinator. This was a remarkable problem solving opportunity; it taught me well how to train and lead small and large groups.

Aided in creation of logistical procedures for catering department

Carolina Sign, Inc. 2008 - 2011

Intern 2011

This job showed me where my future and started my path through this school of art. Originally came to the store during a job shadow, I showed enough aptitude to be signed on as a designer for the company. Here we produced signs and advertising graphics in-house for corporate contracts and the Mom-n-Pop Shop down the street.

Only intern brought on install team

EDUCATION and CERTIFICATES

Diploma Attended

Nation Ford High School, Fort Mill, SC

York Technical College

Digital Art and Design, Future Business Leaders of America Advertising Design

Certificates

- Certiport—Adobe Certified Expert
 - O Adobe Creative Cloud—Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign
 - o Adobe Creative Suite 5—Photoshop, Illustrator, Dreamweaver, Flash
- Certiport—Microsoft Office Specialist
 - o Microsoft Office 2010—Word, Excel, Access